Speaker 1: Adut Akech was born in Sudan on Christmas Day.
Her debut as a model was in a local fashion show.
She appeared on the cover of British Vogue for the March 2024 issue,
which celebrated 40 icons in the fashion industry.
Speaker 2: Paul Mescal is an Irish actor.
His mother was a police officer and his father was a schoolteacher.
The eldest of three children, he has a brother and a sister.
He starred in Gladiator II, Ridley Scott’s sequel to the 2000 historical drama.
Speaker 3: Billie Eilish and her older brother were homeschooled,
a decision their parents made to spend time with them
and give them the freedom to pursue their interests, including art, dancing, and acting.
Eilish did some acting auditions, but she disliked them and preferred to concentrate on music.